I found you by the water.
[music and singing] It was no surprise.
Both got high. Then the tides rising.
[singing]
[music]
We're just too [music] small for the
starry sky. [singing]
Making love better than a compromise. I
know. [music]
I know.
[music] Find [singing] you by the
mountains. They were supposed to fall.
Are you still there if you miss my call?
[singing and music]
Just too small for the empty
[music and singing] space. Better off
holding my breath. fading away.
[singing and music]
>> So I'll just fade away. [music]
[singing]
>> I'll just fade away. Yeah.
[music]
>> All right,
baby. I'll fade away.
Tiny desk.
[applause]
>> We made it, man.
Thank you all so much for joining us. My
name is Macys. These are my pals. We're
going to play you guys some songs. I've
been waiting a long time to be here.
Hope you enjoy it [music] very much. I
don't want to wake up
from sleeping [music] in this [singing]
same bed every day.
Oh, the storm been coming.
[music and singing] And I ain't going to
stay.
Keep on trying to get out my own
[singing] way.
[music] How many times should
should I pass on by that [singing] big
old willow tree
just to prove that there ain't nothing
[music and singing] here for me.
and led me on my way. So cheerfully.
[music]
So cheerfully. [singing]
Come on. So cheerfully.
Is it something [singing] in the way?
Oh, she [music] telling me a tree. Lord
knows I'm trying. [singing]
I'm singing. [music] I just got to draw
the light and go get my peace [singing]
of mind. Lord knows I'm trying.
Oh no. Singing. Is [music and singing]
it something in the way? Oh, she didn't
be a change. Lord knows [singing] I'm
trying. [music]
Oh,
I just got to turn and go [music] get my
peace of [singing] mind. Lord knows I'm
trying.
[music] Oh no.
Lord knows I've been trying, [singing]
friend. L knows I've been trying. Lord
knows I've been [music] trying, friend.
L knows [singing] I've been trying. L
knows [music] I've been trying, friend.
Knows I've been trying. L knows
[singing and music] I've been trying,
friend. Knows I've been trying, friend.
[music]
>> Thank you. [applause]
>> [music]
[music]
>> We've been driving all night.
Couldn't see with my headlights on. I
know something [singing] ain't right
when [music] she don't have to [singing]
stay so long. Trying to bend [music]
into the sun. [singing]
Progress
[music] how you float into the shade.
>> [music and singing]
[music]
>> When you come, [singing]
it's what you [music] don't say.
Baby, when you come,
it's what you don't [music and singing]
say.
I'm putting this thing right back
[music] together
myself, [singing]
right?
I'm putting this thing right back
together [music]
myself.
I [music and singing]
know.
[music]
>> [singing and music]
>> heartache. [singing]
Can you save me from this heartache?
[singing]
Thought I made it past the hard days,
[music]
but it only [singing] lasts a while.
Wide awake. [music and singing]
I thought I felt the earth
shake. [music and singing]
Still not enough to leave a
[singing and music] lonely place for
only after day. No.
[music]
So [singing] tell me
whatever [singing]
happened to me or you. [music]
>> [singing]
>> telling
[music]
you never [singing] used to overink
things through. [singing]
Comfortable enough [music]
or at least I [singing] have my fun as a
color fades to black. I would [music]
take the [singing] whole thing back.
Baby, when the sky starts caving in, at
least [singing and music] I said I saw
it coming.
[music]
Oh,
comfortable [singing]
enough. Or at least [music]
my father as a color turns to gray.
[singing]
I would throw it all away
[music] when the wall start closing in.
At least I said I [singing] saw it
coming.
>> [music]
>> away
from it. [singing and music]
>> Throw it all away
from
bless.
[music]
[singing]
Throw [music] it all away.
as they come around. [singing]
Let [music] it be for now.
For now,
[music]
so I've been working on my new album.
[singing]
This is from my new album coming out
someday. But I wrote [singing] this uh
with [music] my good friend and tiny
desk veteran cartoons. I hope you enjoy.
[singing]
>> Packed up your things and went to get
gone. Looks like this things to figure
out alone. Couple weeks left and I'm
back on the road. [singing]
Running low on emotional show. I've been
learning [singing] what I already know.
>> But these nights never felt so low.
[music and singing]
I hope you find what you're looking for.
Girl, you [music and singing] make me
want to sail the sunrise. Your lips
puckered like a loaded gun. The fear of
missing out got you [music] missing out.
A baby.
Girl, you make me want to catch the
moon. The next [singing] time never
comes too soon. I scream it out in hopes
they hear me, too. [singing] loving.
[music]
Please
come home
tonight. [music]
Please
come on baby [singing and music]
tonight
cuz I miss [music and singing] you,
darling. N
come home.
>> Won't you [music] come on home tonight?
[singing]
[music] Right.
Please
come on baby [singing]
tonight. [music]
[singing]
Please darling. Oh said it won't be
long. Still trying to walk around like
[music and singing] I don't need it. No.
No. Said it won't be long. I wait for
you to call [singing and music] me. Need
you in the worst way. I said it won't be
long. Still trying to walk around like I
don't [music and singing] need no. Said
it won't be long. I said it won't be
said it won't be.
And I hope you going to let me [music]
show [singing]
>> no other days that I will be on
[singing]
the call [music]
you know
>> and I hope you going to let me know.
[singing]
Should I say should [music] I get
I get [music]
tiny desk. Y'all ready to dance a little
bit?
>> [music]
>> Well, let's boogie there.
[music]
Come on.
Let's go.
She don't [music and singing] like the
rain.
She don't like [music] things crashing
down. She don't She won't make [music] a
play.
I bet that I [music] could show you how.
Saw her burning [singing] on the street.
[music]
>> That's right.
>> Smoke's my testimony. [singing]
>> Smoke's my testimony. Just don't stand
[music] so close to me. Nah nah nah nah
[singing] nah. Yeah. Unless the night
shall [music] be my only
my only. Come on. Singing. She got her
own way to make things go. [music] All
of the things I tried to keep low.
Feeling like I've been changing. So what
you doing being a stranger? [singing]
[music] Singing. I got a ticket but I
can't go. I need a place I can call my
home. [singing and music]
So tell me where you go tonight.
[music and singing]
Where you go tonight?
[music]
Come on. Could I be the one [singing] to
do the things that you like? Where you
going tonight?
>> Oh no. [music] Where [singing] you going
tonight?
Could I be the one to do the
[singing and music] things that you
like? Let's go. The things you like. The
[singing] things you like. Now clap your
hands now. The things you like. The
[music and singing] things you like to
do. The things you like. The things you
like to do. All the things [singing] you
like. [music]
The things you like to do. All the
things you like. The things you like.
You [music]
like the
[singing and music] things you
like. You [music]
like [singing] the things you like.
One time for the [music] band real
quick, please. Over
[music]
here on the keys, we got Dan Abraham
on guitar. Josh Porter
[music]
behind me on the drums. We got Brian
Richberg Jr.
Over here on the bass. And steering this
musical ship, we got Declan
[music and singing] Meyers. Give it up.
on BGVs and the Tambourine Man, Brandon
Lee Harris. Come on. [music]
Also on the BGVs over here, we got Jess
Schneider. Let's go.
[music]
Thank you so much. I'm Mac. We got one
more for you tonight.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Uh, this song right here changed my life
and I've been waiting. [music] It turns
10 years old next year. So, I've been
waiting uh quite a long time to play
this [music] one. If you know it, let's
sing it together. Tiny desk.
[music]
Oh, you heard
[music] what they [singing] say.
Oh, the more things change, the more
[singing] they stay the same. [music]
I hear y'all. Don't be shy.
Said, "Ain't that a shame?"
[singing and music]
>> I know it's a shame.
I've been good. [singing]
>> I've been [music] good
>> for some time. Sometimes
>> I'd be lying if I [singing and music]
said that you went on my mind.
Just [music] trying to [singing] give it
some time.
[music]
Feeling [singing] like I'm running
running
[music]
away. [singing]
I never had the chance [singing]
to [music]
say
right.
I can say that love you. [music] It's
[singing] easy. I don't need to prove a
[music] single thing.
Somewhere [singing] along the way, I
guess [music]
you got under my skin.
[music and singing]
I put all my cards out on the table.
You ain't never going to show [singing]
your hand.
I would rather hold you close than
[singing] try to understand.
>> [music]
>> Morning [singing] sun.
>> Morning sun.
>> Morning high.
>> Morning high. [singing and music]
>> Oh, I think this haze is fin. My best
disguise. [singing]
That's right.
>> [music]
>> No need to think about why.
[music]
What you say [singing]
star
[music]
how [singing] you love to smile and
watch the clouds reside.
Just trying to give it some [singing]
time.
Feeling like I'm [singing and music] run
running
[music] away. [singing]
Never had the chance [music and singing]
not
chance to say.
[singing]
Come on y'all. Let's go. I can say that
love with you is easy.
[singing and music]
I don't need a proof. every single
thing.
[music] Somewhere along the way,
[singing] I guess you got under [music]
my skin.
And I put all my cuts out [music] on
[singing] the table.
You ain't never going [music] to show
your hand.
I [singing] would rather hold [crying]
you close [music] than try to
understand.
[music]
And I put all my cuts out on the
[singing] table. [music]
You ain't never going that show your
hand.
I would [music and singing] rather hold
you close than try to [music]
understand.
I try to [singing] understand.
I want to [singing] try to understand.
[music]
said, "I'll [singing] try
to understand it."
[singing]
[music]
Tiny does. Thank you so much.
[cheering]
One more time for the band behind me.
Come on. [applause]
Thank you.
[cheering]
>> [applause]
[applause]
>> Thank you guys.
>> A quick update before you go. We're
doing another Tiny Desk giveaway. Enter
by September 12th, 2026, [music] and you
and a friend could win a free trip to DC
to see a Tiny Desk concert live in
person. You even get to choose which
upcoming show [music] you want to see.
And it's completely free to enter. Just
go to npr.org/tinyes
giveaway. Entering is completely free,
but you can get more entries by snagging
some limited edition Tiny Desk merch or
by making a special donation to the NPR
network. Learn more and enter today at
npr.org/tinyes [music]
giveaway.